One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
The Hope and Despair of the Skeleton
and the Straw Hats' Counterattack!
Bastard!
Give my shadow...!
Settle down!
Moriah isn't here!
Is this...?
The Sunny.
The Sunny?!
Why're we back here?
No, but...
I'm not dreaming.
I've lost my shadow!
What a weird feeling.
Hey, big trouble!
Life or death situation!
There's no food left!
The only provisions we had are gone.
They took all the food we've been stocking.
Cheese and crackers are not enough for me!
Meat!
How shameful...
I let my guard down.
I even lost my pirate lunch...
Cheese is not enough... not enough...
By the way,
I don't see Nami-san anywhere.
She was kidnapped?!
Why didn't you chase her to the end of the earth?!
I-I'm sorry.
But, we were in a critical situation and we couldn't go after her.
Who and where the hell is he?!
I'll go save her this instant!
W-Wait!
Let me explain everything first.
Listen, I'll make it short.
Right now, there are two things we must get back no matter what!
Food.
Nami.
Then our shadows, right?
That's three.
That's not how you're supposed to rank them.
First, let me explain about Nami and the shadows.
Ma-!
Marry?!
Don't mess around!
So damn unforgivable!
He sure is brave to marry Nami.
And also, I'm a giant?!
They made such a zombie?!
So, Luffy's and the cook's zombies have been confirmed, Usopp?
I never thought he was one of the Seven Warlords...
I'm scared all of a sudden.
You didn't know?
I see.
If zombies resemble oneself, then...
I've also seen Zoro's zombie.
What's he like?
He was just like you.
He was wearing wooden clogs so, I knew it wasn't you.
Well, it doesn't matter.
If we find those three zombies and throw salt in their mouths, we'll get our shadows back, right?
Anyway, good thing you found such a weakness.
The one who told us about their weakness and told us to come here and rescue you... was that skeleton.
You met Brook?!
Yeah, we did.
And I asked him a foolish question shortly afterwards...
To be honest, the first time you said he'd tag along as one of our friends, I completely disagreed.
The more I talked with that clattering skeleton, I realized he really has bones.
Although he's a skeleton.
He's a real man!
Wait a minute!
While we're still at it, just answer me one more question.
If you go out in public with that look of yours, you know how people will react, right?
You're a talking skeleton, you know.
There's no way someone will befriend a guy with such evil looks.
Hideous things always get despised.
Franky, what're you...?
Even if you manage to escape this cursed sea...
You're aware of your fate.
Decades of despair, unable to escape...
You said you were so lonely you wished to die, right?
If I were you, I'd no longer cling to life.
Having such insignificant existence and acting all chivalrous all the time...
Just tell us what're you hiding already.
To go that far... what do you want to achieve?
What is that promise you made to your friends that you talk about?
You're a very nosy person.
It's simple.
Long ago, our pirate crew left one of our friends behind at a certain place.
It was a very painful farewell, but...
As our ship departed, we promised we'd return no matter what.
Then, we were annihilated on this sea...
In order to not leave our promise unfulfilled....
As the only member of the crew who has lived long enough, I have the duty to inform him of these events.
Since the day of our deaths...
It's been 50 years I presume.
50 years?!
Hey! That was too long ago! I wasn't even born yet!
Sorry to say but, there's no way that guy could've waited such a long time!
Why would he wait for me?
He has the right to leave and not be kept waiting.
If by any chance he believed in our promise and has been waiting this whole time...
I can't imagine how lonely he must feel...
If he's been waiting this whole time while thinking we betrayed him...
I can't imagine how miserable he must feel!
You...
The name of the friend to whom we swore to meet again on that cape is...
Laboon.
We couldn't take a little whale on our dangerous journey...
Take care, Laboon!
We'll definitely come back for you!
I suppose he must've grown a lot by now...
Is your friend...
A whale...?
Correct.
I can't help but think he has believed in us since then.
He might be thinking that we'd play our cheerful music as always...
And return for him with open arms.
I cannot ask for forgiveness after we died so irresponsibly.
I cannot call him from the afterlife, after our reckless promise...
Dying is not an excuse...!
Because a man once said that they would return no matter what!
That's how it is.
Laboon...
Are you serious?!
It's him...
We've met...
that whale.
You know him?
Why...?
What do you mean?
The Twin Capes located at the entrance of the Grand Line.
That's where we met that huge whale.
It kept bumping it's head against the Red Line, the wall which divides the world.
For 50 years, it waited for its pirate friends who promised to return after doing a lap around the world.
Somehow, Luffy stopped its suicidal habit of hitting itself against that wall.
It still lives...
And keeps waiting for its friends at those capes.
What an amazing story...
Both of them have kept the promise they made 50 years ago!
So, one of the friends Laboon has been waiting for is...
That skeleton.
If you became stronger in these past 5 years...!
I have as well!
That's because our thoughts are the same!
As always, you keep treasuring that afro.
You won't be able to protect such a huge weak point forever.
Shut up!
Laboon...
Do you still remember us?
Whenever I think of how you must feel...
It makes my heart ache...
Although I don't have a heart now!
We were unable to overcome the challenges of the Grand Line.
Our friends have all died.
As for myself...
Not only have I lost my friends...
My face, my body... I've lost everything...
If we ever meet again...
You won't recognize me in the skeleton shape I am now...
Stop!
Not the afro!
I have nothing left, but...
At least... I have this head that looks like Laboon which amused everyone!
Are you brothers?
I'll protect it with my life...!
And we'll definitely meet again...
Please wait for me...
At the promised...
Capes...
Now I love both the skeleton and the whale, damn it!
Shut up!
Now I've made up my mind!
He's a musician...!
A talking skeleton...!
Has an afro...!
That Yohoho thing...!
And he's Laboon's friend!
Even if I have to drag him, I'll make him board this ship!
I'll make him our crewmate!
Do you have any objections?!
Would you change your mind even if we had any?
I really want him to see Laboon again!
Completely agreed, damn it!
Me too, you bastards!
I'm no longer afraid of skeletons!
Now that we're fully aware of the situation...
I'll personally go prevent Nami-san from getting married!
Hey, Zoro!
Where are you going?
Let's get going already.
We gotta recover an extra shadow now, don't we?
Alright!
Men, get ready to counterattack!
We're pulverizing Thriller Bark!
Good luck!
You're coming too, idiot!
Anyway, it won't be easy to find the zombies that have our shadows.
Also,
Luffy's zombie is extremely huge!
It's bigger than two giants!
You can't hope to beat that thing!
We don't need to search for the zombies.
Though, I wanna see mine.
What're you talking about?!
If we stay like this, we'll never get close to the sunlight again.
But, don't you remember...?
The old zombie man said it, didn't he?
I just saw you...
You're terribly strong!
So...
What request?
I want you to beat a certain man...
I'm sure you can do it!
Despite the number of victims, if you beat him, everyone will be saved!
If we take out Gekko Moriah, everyone's shadows will return!
H-He did say that...
There he goes again... right to the point...
Then...
If we climb those stairs, we'll find Moriah, right?
Certainly!
Anyway...
I'll go kick Gekko Moriah's ass!
Since that'll bring everyone's shadows back...
Sanji, I'll leave Nami up to you.
But of course!
I don't care whether he is an invisible man or a ceramic man!
I'll kick the hell out of him right through the other side of this fog!
Like I'd let that wedding take place!
Ah, I forgot to mention it, but that invisible man saw Nami completely naked in the bathroom.
Whaaaat?!
Bastard!
Don't keep angering him...
He might transform into something.
I feel guilty for letting Nami get kidnapped right before my eyes.
I'll go with Sanji too!
But mostly it's because I don't wanna come across that Warlord again!
That skeleton's fight worries me.
I'll go there.
If Straw Hat beats Moriah first, that'd solve one problem but...
Until that happens, getting killed by his own shadow is a serious matter.
I'll accompany you there, Franky.
I'm curious about how strong this so called "Legendary Samurai" zombie is.
Nami-chan and Skeleton-san...
For the time being they're our priority.
After that, defeating Moriah is definitely the key to victory.
It's not as simple as you say.
Our enemy is one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
No problem.
Crocodile was too.
No problem?!
You were nearly killed!
I beg of you, be careful!
Especially since... I know I already said it, but your zombie is terribly huge!
Alright, alright.
Then, take this.
Carry one bag at least.
It's my Special Zombie-Purifying Salt Ball.
Ah, so this is what you were making a while ago.
Pretty clever.
Anyway...
I've got a word of advice for you all.
No matter how thick the fog is within this sea...
There's no guarantee sunlight won't get through it!
We're only safe because it's midnight!
In other words, when the sun arises at daybreak, that's our ultimate time limit!
That goes without saying!
Reaching daybreak without tasting food is the worst!
We'll make you regret having messed with us!
Gekko Moriah!
We'll take twice the food that was stolen...!
Before daybreak!
No, you see... that's not it...
I mean the limit to recover our shad-
Let's go!
Yeah!
Nami-swan!
Wait a-
Do as you wish then!
I'm coming to rescue you!
Amazing!
So this is a ship!
The sea looks awful...
But my future looks great!
Alright, I'll become the Pirate King with this ship!
Where's Oars right now?
He climbed to the top of the mast, Master.
But... but... Master!
We can't just sit around doing nothing while such a huge zombie wanders aimlessly around the island!
That guy is terribly dangerous!
Don't worry.
It's just a matter of time.
Now that we have Oars, we'll be able to steal the shadows of much stronger warriors.
From now on, we'll have Special Zombies coming one after another!
We'll need stronger marionettes it seems, Hogback.
Leave it to me!
H-Hogback-sama!
We're in trouble!
The pirates...!
What's wrong, Hildon?
The three whose shadows were stolen woke up at the ship and are heading this way with their friends!
What?!
Those who get their shadows stolen can't wake up that quick!
T-Their friends found a way to wake them!
It seems they have some connection with the Humming One!
Perhaps, that man told them what he knew!
All of the pirates knowing how to purify the zombies is proof!
W-What'd you say?!
The zombies fear the pirates...
Currently, they're running from place to place...
The Wild Zombies, Surprise Zombies and Soldier Zombies, couldn't lay a hand on them...
Even before the pirates knew about the salt!
Deploy the General Zombies!
They'll take care of the pirates as long as they don't swallow salt!
And what the hell is Absalom doing?!
Well... you see...
His wedding is about to start right now...
Most of the general zombies are in attendance.
What are those fools doing?!
Come to think of it, he asked if Hogback-sama could give one of his belly dances at the reception in 1 hour.
You're right...
A wedding ceremony is a once in a lifetime memorial event.
That'd be one funny dance-
Like I'd do that now!
Cancel that wedding this instant!
I'm a simple zombie...
I can't go against Absalom-sama...
No need to rely on that beast.
If my ghosts weaken them, the Soldier Zombies will be more than enough to capture them.
Don't panic just because they know the zombies' weakness.
I'll capture every single one of them, so...
Prepare some marionettes for the shadows of the remaining pirates.
I'm going back to my room.
Let's go, Kumashi.
Right away...
That's true.
How reliable.
I expect no less from the Ghost Princess.
What?
It would be best if you learned...
From Kumashi's example.
Anyway...
Everything will be fine, Moriah-sama.
Is that so?
How boring...
Again...?
In any case, you won't have to do anything.
I'll stay here a bit longer.
Oars amuses me more right now.
Then, I have a request.
Since Absalom isn't doing anything, I'd like to take command of just two zombies if it's possible.
They're here!
Where's Moriah?!
Here they come!
Get outta my way!
Give back the food!
Who's the damn bastard who peeked while Nami-san was in the shower?!
Show yourself!
It seems we won't be needing salt for now...
They're rampaging with absolute fury.
I wonder if they even care about the shadows...
C-Commander! There are five people heading for the Dance Hall!
Heading to
Moriah's
Dance Hall
Perona's Room
Heading to
Perona's
Room
Wonder Garden
And we can't handle the two on the bridge below!
Moriah's Dance Hall
It angers me just thinking about me being caught by these weaklings!
If you're so grateful that I freed you, you can start calling me "big bro" if you want.
Like hell!
Oh no! This is bad!
What? What's wrong?
It's all over...
If I were to be reborn, I would want to be a maggot...
I have such large eyebrows... I'm better off dead...
Hey! Luffy, Sanji!
What's wrong with you?!
Robin, what's going on?
It's the ghosts doing!
When you touch them, you lose your will to live.
We haven't found a countermeasure to it...
Alright! I got you now!
Lead Star!
Hurry up!
If they get us too, it'll be over!
The ghosts have almost caught up with us!
No! If we all get caught, it's over!
Set sail! Set sail!
We're falling!
Usopp!
Sanji!
That just now...
No way, that's impossible...
That surprised me.
The stairs are gone!
W-W-What's wrong?!
W-What happened?
The zombies, Usopp and Sanji...
Everyone fell down.
Leaving aside the fact that these two fell down...
What's the meaning of this?
Our path was suddenly blocked.
What's with that wall?
Damn it...!
What the hell happened...?
Just now...?
It isn't stone.
Weapons Left!
What?!
What're you doing?!
A huge wall suddenly appeared.
Idiot! That's no wall!
That's Luffy's zombie!
What?!